difficult...
難しい...
The camera isn't showing anymore, right now.
カメラもう映ってないよ、今
TRUE?
本当?
True, true.
本当、本当
TRUE?
本当?
True, true.
本当、本当
Well then, I'll keep an eye on you.
じゃあ、俺、目を集めておくから
It's only for a moment.
一瞬だけだよ
Just for a moment?
一瞬だけ?
It's a moment.
一瞬だね
Really?
本当に?
close
近い
...
difficult...
難 しい...
secret...
秘密...
secret?
秘密?
Yeah.
うん
So, get on your elbows again.
じゃあ、もう一回、肘ついて
picture?
え?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
I don't say it because I'm embarrassed.
恥ずかしいから言わない
A lifelong wish.
一生の願い
TRUE?
本当?
A lifelong wish.
一生の願い
Really?
本当に?
Yeah.
うん
Just a moment, just a moment.
一瞬だけ、一瞬だけ
Just for a moment.
一瞬だけ
Now put your hand under my foot,
さあ、自分の手をさ、足の下から入れてさ、
Please try to write it.
かくかけるようにしてくれ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Hey, it's close.
ねえ、近いよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Yeah.
うん
Eh, no.
えー、だめ
Well, that's embarrassing.
えー、恥ずかしいよ
Huh?
あれ?
No.
だめ
It's here.
ここになってるよ
Hey, it's close.
ねえ、近い
Strange...
不思議な...
Oh no, no.
やばい、だめ
No.
だめ
That's no good.
それはだめ
No?
だめなの?
No.
だめ
close
近
Yes.
い よ
It's close.
近いよ
Is this it?
これでちゃう?
That's it.
これでちゃう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's dripping again.
また垂れてきたよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
恥ずかしいね
I can't fit it in at all because I'm carrying too much.
背負すぎて全然入んない
It's embarrassing if you touch it with your hands.
手で触ったら恥ずかしいんだよね
What is this?
これなんだろう?
I'm going to put this here.
これを、ここに当てるの
On the other hand, you can guess it yourself.
逆、自分当てていいよ
It's close to my hand.
手に近いよ
You're taking it easy when it comes to guessing.
当てるの、手加減してるでしょ
da
ダ
It's me.
メ だよ
embarrassing
恥ずかしく
No, right?
ない でしょ?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
I don't like this.
これ嫌だ
close.
近い
I've already thought about it.
もう考えた
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいな
It's an athlete's school, right?
選手校でしょ
Good.
よいしょ
Let's go.
ちゃうちゃう
It's embarrassing.
恥 ず かしい
I don't know.
分かんない
shame
恥ず
That's strange.
か しい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It doesn't reach me.
届かない
Huh?
あれ?